朽木字幕组
翻译：
飞越无限
校对：
压制：
月夕诀
注释说明以[ ]表示，一般在视频上部打出
省略句补充以（ ）表示
其他类以【】表示
本片中注释说明均属我个人理解
我来点灯
Let me light the lamp.
我找不到靴子了
I've misplaced my boots.
我把它们放在楼下厨房门边上了
I put them downstairs by the kitchen door.
我睡着了…
I was asleep...
当你拿走它们的时候
when you took them and did that.
－是的 你想让我别那么做么？－不
-Yes. Would you rather I not? -No.
不是
No.
我只是想昨晚上醒着以便我们能聊聊
Only I had intended to be awake last night so we could talk...
聊聊我们要何去何从
which, what with how it's been, we have not done...
在这个自你到达之后的如人所愿的平静的夜晚
in the peace of the evening as I would like, since your arrival.
我喜欢静静的谈话 比如白天过后的晚上
I would enjoy to converse in the stillness, after the day, like that.
今晚我会准备两杯咖啡 我就不会睡着了
Tonight, I will have two cups of coffee, and I will not fall asleep.
早上
In the morning...
我们开始一天的工作前的这段时间
in the quiet before we each take up our work...
也是一段不错的谈话时间
is also a pleasant occasion for such intercourse.
是的
Yes.
今天早上你想开始这个谈话么？
Would you like to start a discussion this morning?
我不想打扰到孩子
I wouldn't want to disturb the boy.
William正熟睡中呢
William sleeps soundly.
若你愿意请关上卧室门 Bullock先生？
If you will see to the bedroom door, Mr Bullock?
我杀了他？
Have I killed him?
首先 死人不会颤抖
First, the dead don't shiver.
其次 你只是做了他让你做的事
And next, you just done what he asked.
导致他到如此地步的原因
And ain't it more likely...
更可能是他下体的疾病
what turned him worse is underlying woe...
而不是试图减轻他的痛苦而插入肛门的手指
than a thumb up his ass attempting his fucking relief?
好了 出去吧
Go on, get the fuck out of here.
你好
Hello.
你是干什么的？
What's your business?
我是Francis Wolcott
I'm Francis Wolcott.
我是Ellsworth,Francis Wolcott先生
My name's Ellsworth, Mr Francis Wolcott.
－你能听到我说话么？－当然 先生 你好？
-Can you hear me? -Yes, sir. How do you do?
-我还好 很高兴你能听明白 －是的 先生
-I'm well. Glad you make me out. -Yes, sir.
因为 在GARRET夫人的地盘上未被准允的
Because them as poke around...
闲逛的行为
Ms Garret's workings without a by-your-leave...
是不被受欢迎的 WOLCOTT先生
ain't welcome, Mr Wolcott...
所以你不应该再延续你的错误了
and you ought not to repeat your fucking mistake.
WELL 无知者无罪
Well, that's an uncivil response to an innocent error.
你年轻的时候是在康斯托克工作么？
Did you work in the Comstock when you was beardless?
是的
I did.
为George Hearst先生看管生意么？
For Mr George Hearst, has a keen eye for the colour?
当Hearst先生的地质专家
As a geologist for Mr Hearst.
WELL 你比我优秀 Ellsworth先生
Well, you have the advantage of me, Mr Ellsworth.
那就有点扯了 WOLCOTT
That ain't a possibility, Wolcott.
你只有一个错误是无辜的
No more than an error of yours would be innocent.
我大致上想起了一个叫Ellsworth的人
I do dimly recall an Ellsworth.
[consolidated Virginia\统一弗基尼亚公司]我认为是这个名字
他管理统一弗基尼亚公司的运营
Superintended the consolidated Virginia operations.
我不会给你答复的
I don't give a fuck what you recall.
那个人是个英雄 没是没夜地挖了一周
A hero. Dug a week without respite...
从塌方中救了三个人
to save three poor souls from the cave-in.
以及46具尸体 从一个就不应该开采的矿洞里
And 46 corpses in a fucking hole that ought never to have been dug.
人总得选择 在计算了收益和风险之后
Always a choice, to count the saved or lost.
给我离开这里
Get off this property!
仅仅当个反对必然变革的人
Just as a man opposed to inevitable change...
不一定就是勒德分子
needn't invariably be called a Luddite.
另一种描述的可能更贴切点
Another choice might be simply to describe him...
比如他适应的慢
as slow in his processes.
你告诉你的老板 他派来的下个代理人
You tell that cocksucker you work for, the next surrogate he sends...
不应该是来自康斯托克
oughtn't to be bloodied from the Comstock.
噪音有点大 不是么 Ellsworth先生？
The noise is terrible, isn't it, Mr Ellsworth?
就像命运一样
Like fate.
"Ox, box, fox."
[索菲亚在学单词]
[意指索菲亚没一心一意的学习
Nora是那个布娃娃]
NORA的注意力没集中
Nora's attentions are wandering.
如果我是你 我就给她一块糖
If I were you, I'd bribe her with candy.
早上好
Good morning.
请进  lsringhausen小姐
Please come in, Miss lsringhausen.
你坐么？
Will you have a seat?
夫人 你还坚持你的想法 想辞退我？
Do you remain of a mind, ma'am, to dispense with my services?
我很尊敬你的教育能力和专业素养
I have immense respect for your training and intelligence,
Isringhausen小姐
Miss lsringhausen...
也很感激你在教育Sofia上倾注的心血
and gratitude for your efforts toward Sofia's education.
性格上 我和你不太合
I am ill-suited temperamentally to collaborate with you...
处在你我的位置上的女人大概都会如此
as women in our positions must do.
我明白
I see.
我提议给你六个月工资的解雇费
I propose to pay you six months' wages severance...
和额外的200美元以抵偿
and an additional $200 against...
你来回的费用
the expense for your journey here and return to Chicago.
在你在此等待安排期间
While you're making your arrangements...
我也会继续支付你在旅馆的房费
I will also continue to pay for your room here at the hotel.
就这些条款而言 Garret夫人
As to those terms, Mrs Garret,
你的提议非常合理
your behaviour is very fair.
lsringhausen小姐 Cotton Mather本来会发现
Miss lsringhausen, Cotton Mather would have found...
这些艰难和不愉快的
hard and joyless...
你如此坚定地施加于
the standards you so resolutely apply to
我和Sofia之上的评判准则
me and Sofia...
以及 当然 还有评判你自己的标准
and, of course, to yourself.
我祝福你
I wish you very well.
多谢 夫人
Thank you, madam.
－你要…  －我不和Sofia道别了
-Would you… -I'll not say goodbye to Sofia...
以免她伤心
to spare her upset.
-Dan.  -E.B.
－来点咖啡？ －好的
-Coffee? -Please.
我就直说了 Dan
I'll be candid, Dan.
昨晚我没睡好
I did not sleep well last night.
我听到了从AI房间传出的惨叫
I heard screaming from Al's room.
许多个晚上都有过这情况
Happens up there many a fucking evening.
Well  这次是AI在惨叫 Dan
Well, Al was fucking screaming, Dan.
我很好奇他今早怎么样了
And I'm wondering how he's feeling this morning.
并且你围着那儿绕来绕去 并没有减轻我的担心
And you dancing around the pole ain't allaying my fucking anxieties.
Well  你现在听到他惨叫了么？
Well, do you hear any screams from him now?
不管怎么说 沉默也不是证据
Silence ain't proof either way.
别和我争论 E.B. 否则我扇你个傻逼
Take no tongue with me, E.B., or I'll slap you fucking silly!
他在恢复中 而且还不能接见人
He's on the mend and he ain't fucking receiving.
Well 那就是我问的原因
Well, that's all I was fucking asking.
－那么那就是你的答案 －请传达我的好意
-Then that's your fucking answer. -Convey my joy.
并且告诉他数不尽的好事在等着他呢
And tell him numerous scores await.
温暖的一天  Dan？
Soft-fucking day, Dan.
Crop Ear 早上好
Morning, Crop Ear.
对不起 Eamon
Sorry, Eamon.
[他叫的是那个人的外号]
好好看看 这儿不是重新长出来了么？
Take a good look. Ain't growing back.
－他怎么样了？ －AI早上出去了
-ls he about? -Al's out early.
去Gayville看个地方
Look at a place in Gayville.
Oh, yeah？
Oh, yeah?
你一定要抓住眼前的运气 Dan
You must seize fortune by the forelock, Dan.
那就是我来这儿的原因
That's why I'm here,
把一件美事送到他的面前
to put a matter before him.
－你知道的 我不会浪费他的时间的
You know I'll not waste the man's time.
－是的 你不会
-No, you won't.
你总是有你的办法 Dan
That's some fucking way you have about you, Dan.
现在 你要么告诉我们俩你的事
Now, you could either say your piece to me and Johnny...
要么就滚出这里
or you can get the fuck out of here.
我会很高兴地说这事
I'll say it gladly...
希望你会把我的话递给他
and hope you'll commend my words to him...
那个在Gayville的人 要在第一时间告诉
who's in Gayville, at the earliest opportunity.
我在酝酿一场行动
I contemplate a piece of activity.
我需要找几个可靠的人
I need to organise some reliable fellows...
埋伏在合适的地方伏击黄金运输队
Iocate a right place to waylay that metal.
我会告诉他的
I'll let him know.
四分之一
Twenty-five percent.
整整四分之一的全部收益会进Al Swearengen的口袋
One full quarter of the proceeds in total go to Al Swearengen...
归Gem Saloon酒吧
the Gem Saloon...
或者你和Johnny  作为预防人手
or you and Johnny, as the fucking case may be.
你可能需要抠抠耳朵了
You may need to clean the wax out of your holes...
因为我说了我会让他知道的
because I said I will let him know.
你感觉我什么时候能得到回复？
When do you suppose I could expect a favour of a response?
明天下午
Tomorrow afternoon.
那么他在Gayville过夜？
He's overnight in Gayville then?
那就明天下午吧
Then tomorrow afternoon it is.
说出来他的具体去向 我现在感觉
Getting particular of where he was gone, I realise now...
这是个错误  突然间我感到不安
was a fucking mistake, which happened because I'm so fucking upset.
由此来看 我得处理掉这个耳朵不好使的家伙了
From this point forward, I'll handle that earless cunt.
顶上的两个包
Top two bags.
－要我帮你拿包么 小姐？ －不 不用了
-May I help you with your bags, miss? -No, you can't.
别看我 别和我说话 直到我洗完澡
Or look at me or talk to me until I've took a bath.
他指的是泥泞的大道]
沿着沼泽 夫人
Follow the quagmire then, ma'am.
你要去的地方是右边最后的那个
The establishment you want is the last on the right.
把这个女士的行李拿到Chez Ami去
Take this lady's luggage to the Chez Ami.
好的 先生
Yes, sir.
别看她 也别和她讲话 直到她洗完澡
Do not look at her or talk to her until she's bathed.
Wolcott先生
Mr Wolcott.
骗人的假晴天  弥漫着毁灭性的谣言
Deceptively fair weather, given the devastating rumours.
小点声 Farnum先生
Less volume, Mr Farnum.
－则更有说服力 －好的
-More conviction. -Yes.
－你的旅馆？ －是的 先生
-Your hotel? -Yes, it is, sir.
－你的行李？ －是的
-Your luggage? -Yes.
也许我会给它们安排个好的房间
May I install it in one of our better rooms?
请
Please.
帮我指下Bella Union
Direct me to the Bella Union.
不足50码 有阴茎露着乱晃的地方
Not 50 yards as the bird flies...
或者有精虫入脑的男人的地方
or a man who is lead on by his prick...
或者有要试试手气的人的地方
or needing to test his luck.
房间我写谁的名字
To whom shall I assign the room?
Hugo Jarry.
E.B. Farnum 旅馆所有人
E.B. Farnum, owner-proprietor.
也是市长 尽管很大程度上是名义上的
Also mayor, though that position is largely ceremonial.
劳伦斯郡特派员 名副其实的
Lawrence County Commissioner. The position is real.
Hello,Jarry,特派员Jarry
Hello, Jarry. Commissioner Jarry.
特派员Jarry 好吧 只是近五天才任命的
Commissioner Jarry now, yes, as of the last five days.
很高兴在这儿见到你 Adams
Delighted to find you here, Adams.
你本来是能知道我的下一站的
You could have known my next whereabouts...
如果你愿意接见我而不是让我在你办公室外坐了
if you'd talked to me in Yankton where I sat outside your office...
半天
for half a fucking day.
似乎杨克顿的很多人
It seemed to many of us in Yankton...
都还沉浸在地方官Clagett失踪的悲痛中
that in the aftermath of Magistrate Clagett's disappearance...
(相对于我们的选择) 你选择了不同的同伴
you chose different companions.
我最后一次看到Clagett是他和Crook将军
Last I saw Clagett, he rode in here
骑马到这里
with General Crook.
我感觉他们也是一起离开了
I figured he left with him, too.
也可能随后遭到了
And perhaps was plucked up...
土族人的袭击
subsequently from amidst the troops by savages.
这种月夜偷袭符合他们的作风
Such moonlight treachery being their stealthy hallmark.
也可能他拿了某个人的贿赂跑了 没回去述职
Maybe he took a bribe from someone, didn't hold up his end...
罪有应得
got his just desserts.
那就不是我或者杨克顿的任何一个人感兴趣的了
That's of no personal interest to me or anyone in Yankton...
只是你择友的问题
any more than your choice of companions.
如果你在州长行动之前
If you're trying to freeze out Swearengen...
逼死了Swearengen 你就打错算盘了
before the Governor makes his play, you are betting the wrong way.
[反讽Adams]
某些人肯定是
Someone certainly is.
不管怎样我会告诉他我看到你了
Anyways, I'll tell him I saw you.
我日程紧  否则我会亲自登门拜访
I have a close schedule. Otherwise, I'd pay the respects myself.
我在想你是否会让我过去
I wonder if you will let me pass.
Marvin 我只是希望你没受谣言影响 不是么？
I only hope, Marvin, you ain't privy to information，ain‘t I.
600美金 Tolliver先生
$600 US, Mr Tolliver.
函待开发的16号矿区土地所有权
Claim 16 above discovery.
那并没有回答我刚才问你的 年轻人
That ain't responsive to my previous fucking statement, young man.
我来告诉你 先生 我个人情况不妙
I tell you what, sir. It's the fucking
【下面是ALTITUDE】
altitude that's got to me.
我明白
I see.
我流鼻血以及其他的症状
Nosebleeds and every fucking thing else.
Well 你的健康第一
Well, your health's got to come first.
Leon!
拿我包里的文件来
Light as my kit's got...
我们成交了
we can go ahead and say done.
-$600 Con. -都在这了 先生
-$600, Con. -Right here, sir.
上帝啊 不是给我
Jesus Christ, don't pay it to me.
Marvin会杀了咱俩的
Marvin here will shoot us both.
-拿好 Marvin -你会写字么 Marvin？
-Here you go, Marvin. -You lettered, Marvin?
我会在上面画个叉 先生
I'm up to making my X, sir.
-Con 你来当公证人  -好的 我会的
-Con, you sign as a witness. -Will do, sir.
当我画叉的时候别在我肩膀上看着
Don't be looking over my shoulder when I'm signing my fucking X.
别再和我说 你感到意外
Don't ever say that to me again. You surprised yourself.
事情就是如此而已
It's what happened.
我不想听到这事被提及是因为它熏黑了我的思想
I don't want to hear it spoken of because it darkens my thoughts.
-关于你和谁合作？ -不错
-About who you're partnered with? -Exactly.
他们都是下半身的动物
They get led by their dicks.
我们也有自己的特有武器 而我们却丢了这仅有的优势
Our cunts lead us, we lose our only edge.
你担心的事是不会发生的
That wasn't what was going on.
还不糟糕么？ 他让你生气了么 Joanie？
Was it worse? Were you angry at him, Joanie?
那是你感到惊讶的么？
Was that what surprised you?
你有多生气啊
How angry you were...
乔治·赫斯特的二把手是个残忍而邪恶的人
that George Hearst's second was a cruel and evil man?
你有想到你杀了他可能会让我们这些人偿债么？
Did you think maybe you'd shoot him to get us little people even?
我带着枪进去是为了保护自己
I took that gun into the room with me to protect myself.
谁让你和他一起进那个房间的？
Who fucking asked you to go into the room with him?
没有人来算账 我们都得死
Nobody gets even. We get dead.
但在我离开之前 我想好了一个长久的舒适的退休生活
But before I go, I intend a long and comfortable retirement...
并且要这个混蛋来赔付退休金
and that cocksucker's gonna pay the freight.
会有可怕的事在这儿发生么？
Something terrible is going to happen here.
你甚至都不知道他要杀害哪个姑娘
You don't even know the girl he wants to harm.
你要置身事外
You stay the fuck out of it.
他指示你了
He tipped you!
这个地方问起来臭死了
This whole place smells like shit.
人现实点并不是背信弃义 Richardson.
It is no disloyalty to be a realist, Richardson.
我们都是凡夫俗子
We are mortal.
满怀希望 坚持不懈
One hopes for the best. One perseveres.
时常自省 但是如果人不现实那他就是个屁
One re-evaluates constantly. One is an asshole if one doesn't.
扩大化的忠诚并不等同于背叛的忠诚
Loyalty expanded is not loyalty betrayed.
我不是想对Al Swearengen不忠诚
I contemplate no disloyalty to Al Swearengen.
我感到无处躲避
I feel exposed.
我不喜欢无力感 但我知道我现在很无力
I don't like being weak, and I know that I am.
我渴望有个强大的精神支柱来依靠
I yearn to rely on a stronger will.
在缺乏它的时候 我对我能干的事感到恐惧
I fear what I'm capable of in its absence.
然而你 Richardson 一点都不了解自己
Whereas you, Richardson, know nothing of yourself.
是拉屎 还是眼睛瞎了 是用脚走 还是骑马？(你都不知道)
Are you shitting or going blind? Or on foot or horseback?
你个肮脏的笨蛋
You vile, fucking lump!
把那些碎料包在肉馅土豆馅饼里
Bury that offal in the Shepherd's Pie.
该死的
God damn it!
今天我可以上去了么？
May I go up today?
-要多久我才能得到回复？ -要留消息么？
-How long is my fucking sentence? -Any messages?
咱俩有可能不以血相见么？
Is there any fucking chance you and me don't end up in blood?
等你看到太阳没有升起
Any of you realising that the sun don't rise
或者没有照到咱俩身上的时候
and set on me and you?
什么意思？
What the fuck does that fucking mean?
就是说可能会有其他的因素
Means there may be other fucking factors...
改变我的决定
factored into my decision-making.
除了那个 个人认为
Besides the fact that I find you to
还有可能的是我发现你没胆了
be a pain in the balls, personally.
请上报：来自杨克顿的特派员
Please report: Commissioner Jarry from Yankton
已经到营地了Jarry
has arrived to the camp...
准备爆AI的菊花
and intends to fuck Al up the ass.
就是说那个特派员也会这样对你 是么？
Said he to you while doing the same?
这事儿很重要
It is important that he hear that.
你要想帮倒忙就别禀报
You do him disservice not to tell.
听着 Adams.
Listen, Adams.
AI情况很糟
Al is fucked up bad.
可能要死
Maybe dying.
-上帝啊 -诅咒的对 上帝啊
-Jesus. -Goddamn right, Jesus.
膀胱结石堵住了他的尿道口
Them stones have done plumb blocked off his piss passage.
擦
Fuck!
-好吧 好吧 -全都指望着他呢
-Okay. All right. -It's all backed up in him.
HEY 该死的 他的尿都憋到肺的位置了
Hey, shit, he's got piss in his lungs.
-他能说话么？ -不能 他不能说话
-Can he talk? -Fuck no, he can't talk.
他只能茫然地躺在那里发抖
He just lays there and shivers and stares at nothing.
当医生虐待他的尿道的时候他叫出来了
He screams when Doc abuses him with them fucking prick poles of his.
很抱歉我误会你了
Sorry I broke your balls.
我会留心让他知道你的消息的
I'll see to it he gets your news...
如果他恢复到我认为他能理解我的意思的程度
if he gets to a point I think he can understand my meaning.
对了 你的那个兄弟怎么样了
Listen, how's your little buddy,
就是那个我打了的？
the one I put the beating on?
-Hawkeye. -Yeah, Hawkeye.
他还活着
He'll live.
不管怎地 什么东西
It's something, anyway.
-早上好 夫人 -早上好 Ellsworth先生
-Morning, ma'am. -Good morning, Mr Ellsworth.
不好意思我迟到了
I'm sorry I'm late.
希望你度过了一个平静的夜晚
I hope you spent a restful night.
是的 我原谅你了
I did. And you're forgiven.
但是今早 我注意到充斥着大量的混乱
But this morning, I note an amount of confusion...
和忧虑 以及有关杨克顿
and anxiety abound, and words of panic...
处理土地证明的恐慌的言词
about Yankton's disposition of the claims.
恐慌是比短柄铲更容易传递的
Panic's easier on the back than the short-handled shovel.
我明白
I see.
Garret夫人 造物者以他的无限智慧完成他的工作
The Creator, in His infinite wisdom, Mrs Garret, salted His works...
所以有黄金的地方就会有谣言
so that where gold was there also you'd find rumour.
尽管他秉持公正 但福祸总是相倚的
Though, He decreed just as firm that the opposite wouldn't always hold.
你要知道我不需要
You understand I needn't be comforted...
用真相来安慰
at the expense of the truth.
夫人 我迟到是因为我从矿场驱逐了一个人
I'm late, ma'am, over shooing a man away from your digging's...
他叫Francis Wolcott 为George Hearst寻觅财富
named Francis Wolcott, that scouts for George Hearst...
如果他不认为有利可图的话
who wouldn't spare attention for a camp or the sun itself...
他不会吝惜精力在营地上
if he didn't think it likely to fill his coffers.
他也不会是在谎言前畏缩
Nor the sort who'd shrink from a lie...
为了实现自己目标
or more than one, to advance his purpose...
而不知道怎样传播谣言的那类人
or be ignorant of how to circulate his falsehoods...
没有人知道谣言出自哪里
without anyone knowing their source.
现在我来到营地听到水在变混
And now I come to camp to hear the waters called muddy...
并且越来越快 尽管我没有看到这水有什么变化
and the current quickened, though I see no change in the creek.
而傻瓜们
And the hooples...
当然会断定洪峰在快速逼近
certain sure the flood crest fast approaches...
已经开始这样想了
have begun to think keenly...
我要赶在事情发生之前
"I'll get ahead of the event.
也许我要低价卖掉土地债权
"Maybe I'll sell my claim at discount."
放弃所有以便他们能跑到高地上去
Anything to unharness so they can head for the higher ground.
我个人想法 夫人
Myself, ma'am...
我赌土地证明的效力会被保留
I'd be betting that the levy will hold.
妈妈 你和Bullock先生提了么？
Did you speak of it to Mr Bullock, Mama?
-还没呢 William -今天你会提么？
-Not yet, William. -Will you speak of it today?
早上好 Bullock先生
Good morning, Mr Bullock.
早上好
Good morning.
燕麦粥 给Seth带么？
Oatmeal, Seth?
好的 Martha
Please, Martha.
Bullock先生 妈妈想要个菜地
Mr Bullock, Mother was wanting a kitchen garden...
我来照看
which I would have care of.
你选好地方了吗？
Have you chosen a spot yet?
我在房子后面用脚量了一块
I paced one out in the back of the house, sir.
昨天我本来要修整土地的
Yesterday, I would have broken the ground...
但是被工具阻住了
but from wanting the tools.
你想现在就去告诉Star先生么？
Would you like to go now and tell Mr Star...
你需要铲子 锄头和耙子
you need shovel, hoe and a rake?
是的
Yes, sir.
你能想起怎么走么？
Do you recall your way to the hardware store?
能 先生
I do, sir.
我现在去行么 妈妈？
Is it okay if I go now, Mama?
-Garret夫人 -Faenum先生
-Mrs Garret. -Mr Farnum.
Garret夫人？
Mrs Garret?
什么样的男人会慷慨地交易自己的智力优势
What male would not trade our small superiority of intellect...
来换取
to possess that...
女性的直觉
gift of intuition so bountifully bestowed on the lesser sex?
Farnum先生 你的话我不明白
Mr Farnum, your meaning is beyond me.
夫人 我想像着 某天早上你突然醒来
I imagine you, madam, awakening the other morning...
毫无缘由地
suddenly and for no earthly reason...
相信营地处在危险之中
convinced the camp was at peril.
我的黄金应该存在丹佛
"My gold should be spirited to Denver"...
我想像着也许是当你梳头时 毫不担心这类事
I imagine you thinking, maybe as you brushed your hair...
你在想着
and without worrying the conviction or studying upon it...
送走黄金
sending the gold away.
处于危险之中？ Farnum先生 这个营地么？
At peril? Mr Farnum, the camp?
你的话我不明白
Your meaning is beyond me.
夫人 如果努比亚的鬼怪在我的支配之下
Ma'am, if a Nubian genie were at my disposal...
我会看到他的黑手划过我的旅馆上方
I'd see his great nigger fingers whisk up my hotel...
押在丹佛 就是你处理黄金的地方
and deposit it in Denver, just as you did your gold.
因为营地处于危险之中？
Because the camp's at peril?
是的 夫人 是的 危险
Yes, madam, yes. Peril.
甚至比那更糟
And worse than peril.
也许你应该卖了旅馆？
Perhaps you should sell.
Garret夫人 我明白你意思 但我不会的
Mrs Garret, had I your intuition, would I not have done.
我会买下来的
I'll buy it.
你不是很惊讶那种直觉和慷慨么？
Aren't you wonderful and kind and intuitive and generous.
不 我不能拖累你 也不能利用你的慷慨之心
No, I couldn't burden you, nor impose upon your generosity...
尽管你很富裕
tremendously wealthy as you are.
Farum先生 说出你的要价吧 我们要关闭交易了
Name your price, Mr Farnum. We'll close the transaction now.
夫人 你这是在捣乱  在戏耍我
Madam, now you unsettle and trifle with me.
让我紧张、迟疑
And make me nervous and uncertain.
我的意图很明确 不对 应该是直觉
My intention is quite otherwise, and intuition.
Oh 你的直觉？
Oh, your intuition?
出价吧
Name your price.
你们男人怎么干？
How do you males put it?
‘狗屁或者扔下夜壶？’
"Shit or get off the chamber pot?"
Garret夫人 该死地 的确 Oh 天啊
Mrs Garret, shit, indeed. Oh, dear.
除非 Farnum先生
Unless, Mr Farnum....
除非什么 夫人？你要重新考虑？
Unless, what, madam? Do you reconsider?
不 不
No, no.
我明白 这是你的性别优势
I'd understand. It's your sex's prerogative--
我要说的是 除非说的营地处于危险之中的话是在说谎
Unless, I meant to say, you're lying about the camp's peril?
说慌？ 我？
Lying? I?
但为什么你要那么做呢？
But why would you do that?
问的对啊
Exactly.
那你就给我开个价吧
You will make a price for me then.
让我考虑考虑 Garret夫人
Let me consider, Mrs Garret.
别考虑了 Farnum先生 要相信你的直觉
Don't, Mr Farnum. Trust your instincts.
我马上就给盛装打扮的钱
I'll have you in a dress in no time.
可悲的自大的婊子
Miserable, haughty cunt.
[本意是把我置于我的深度之外,也就是不在他善长的领域内了]
把我绕进去了
Putting me beyond my depth.
AI 我们到了关键时候了 我不得不讲一下
We've come to a crisis, Al, and I have to say my piece.
做手术 有两种方法取出石头
The stones can be excised surgically in one of two ways.
所谓的上面的路线就是
The so-called "high method"...
从外阴切入膀胱
which cuts into the bladder from above your penis...
另一种就是从下面进入膀胱
and the other which enters from below.
－下面 什么 医生？ －就是他的阴囊
-Below what, Doc? -His balls.
那么 从下面就是切开经过感染区
So, the "low" entails cutting through his taint.
迄今为止 我观摩过上面路线的实施过程
Now, I have seen the high method performed.
我参加过手术的收尾工作
I assisted at a closing,
并且后来和医生进行了讨论
afterwards discussed it with the surgeon.
想来想去 那是我倾向的方法
Come to it, that is the one that I would prefer.
－AI支持你 －他意下如何？
-Al's with you. -How'd he indicate it?
对前者努力眨眼 对后者却一副愁容
A hard blink for the upper and a scowl for cutting through his taint.
我们要考虑到由专家主刀
With a knife in expert hands...
有十分之二
two men in 10...
的人从手术中活了下来
survive the procedure we contemplate.
但是如果不做手术一直下去到了某种程度
But at what point, without intervention...
你的状况会更糟而让你永远不能恢复
will your condition so worsen as to put you beyond recovery
我确信我们已经快到那个程度了
I believe we have approached that point.
我不是专家 但我会尽全力的
I am not an expert, but I will give it my best effort...
所以如果我们要手术 我来要求你的同意
and I ask you now for your consent, should we need to proceed.
他支持你 医生 他要上面的手术方法
He's with you, Doc. He wants the upper.
Hey 那就是了,最后一次询问,对不对 AI？从上面切开？
Hey, that's it. That's the final call. Right, Al? The upper?
他要上面
He wants the upper.
Well 我感觉你们最好准备一下
Well, I guess you better go make ready.
好的
All right.
好的 和我来 Johnny.
All right. Come with me, Johnny.
－帮我生火 －当然可以 医生
-Help me with this stove. -Sure. Sure, Doc.
在新条约签订前的土地和工作证明
As to claims filed and worked prior to the new treaty...
大体上从山区仍归苏族所有的时间开始算起
in essence from when the hills still belonged to the Sioux...
对其合法性的推测是 会依然
the presumption of legitimacy will apply...
赋予其效力 以便缓和事态
subject to qualification, according to mitigating facts.
简单来讲 没有援引控制原则的情况下
In short, with no controlling principle being invoked...
[我感觉这个原则就是所谓的谁发现就归谁的公认准则]
所有权就会视情况而定
title will be determined on a case-by-case basis.
当土地证明被推翻 新的所有权
When claims are overturned, new title
就会以说好的价格发放
will be awarded at said prices...
通过抽签 给那些允许提交合法申请的人
via lottery, to those submitting verified offers.
我只希望地方政府要排除在资格之外
I only hope territorial officials will be excluded from eligibility.
好的
Yes.
最好告诉你的朋友和亲戚
Better tell your friends and relatives...
[希望官员亲属也不要参与]
把他们的幸运服也要在画卷之外
to pick their lucky suits out for that drawing.
仅仅在Wolcott先生的朋友亲戚这样做了之后
Only after Mr Wolcott's have picked out theirs.
当然 我预计即将到来的司法支持
Of course, anticipation of the forthcoming judicial holding...
可能会很大程度上净化市场
may itself largely cleanse the market.
保持市场的畅通总是更可取的
It's always preferable to allow the market to operate unimpeded.
你们赞成让我说的话
Would that argue for allowing word of my presence...
在营地里流传几天么 在我本人正式现身之前？
to circulate a bit before presenting myself officially?
可以用这段时间熏跑一些人
Man might use that time to put some stink on his johnson.
Hello？
Hello?
这呢 在柜台后面
Down here. Behind the counter.
盘点库存
Taking inventory.
我今天上不了课
I can't do a lesson today.
好吧
All right.
他病得太厉害了
He's too sick.
他可能会死 我不能留下来
Maybe he'll fucking die. But I can't stay.
但是可能留下来学习计算利润明智点
But it'd be smart to stay and learn to calculate fucking interest...
在通融票据上以及那些贴现票据上
on that accommodation paper and those fucking discount notes...
或者其他的什么东西
and whatever the fuck.
换个时间吧 没事的 Trixie.
Another time. It's fine, Trixie.
－我弄疼你的肩了么？ －没有
-Did I hurt your shoulder? -No.
我要走了
I gotta go.
想出去一会儿么？
Want to go out for a bit?
她说Swearengen境况很差
She says Swearengen's bad off.
昨晚我听到他一次次的惨叫
Last night I heard him screaming out again and again.
我猜他越来越糟了
I guess he's worsened with the day.
多谢你给孩子园艺工具
Thanks for outfitting the boy with garden equipment.
他计划回馈我点收成
He's planning to take some prizes come harvest fair.
他提到了玉米和南瓜
He mentioned corn and squash, both.
我有丹佛的消息
I had some news from Denver...
关于我们银行的提议
concerning our proposal on the bank.
我们要提供注册资本的15%
We'd need to find 1 5% of our proposed capitalisation.
如果我们注册两百万我们就要
If we capitalise at the $2 million we figured on--
30万,和丹佛承诺的分开来算
$300,000 separate from what Denver will underwrite.
或者他们以Garret账户做为抵押
Or they'd credit Mrs Garret's accounts as collateral.
不能那么做
Not doing that.
我没提议
I don't advocate it.
我正要告诉你是他们主动提出的
I'm informing you of a communication they volunteered.
我们不能那么做
We're not doing that.
我想我要自己掏腰包了
Suppose I'll have to dip into my own kit, then.
即使这样 到头来还是要剪掉我的头发
Even so, it's back to cutting my own hair.
我会想个办法的
I'll take the idea around.
Swearengen会出钱的
Swearengen would put it up.
臭名昭著的人
Fucking reputable people.
如果钱在流通前必须是干净的
If money had to be clean before it was recirculated...
那我们现在还生活在山洞里
we'd still be living in fucking caves.
－你家老头了说的？ －我说的
-Your old man? -Me.
李先生独家为你提供鸦片
Mr Lee will provide opium to you exclusively...
以便卖给营地里的白人
for sale to whites in the camp.
你会得到Celestial's Alley赌博
You will receive 50% of the gaming proceeds...
[Celestial's Alley应该指中国人的聚居区]
收益的一半
from Celestial's Alley.
我的人会监管收益
My men will lamp the take.
在这解释做生意艰难会劳烦李先生的
It will spare Mr Lee here explaining how slow business was...
比如由于佛陀婚礼记念日什么的
'cause of Buddha's wedding anniversary.
你的人监管收益
Your men lamp the take...
也包括Celestial的妓女生意
also on proceeds from Celestial prostitutes.
－你想要多少妓女？ －你能带来多少？
-How many do you want? -How many can you bring?
多少？
How many?
听起来好像你有无尽的供应似的
That sounds like a man with an inexhaustible supply.
你有多少英国货 我的朋友？
How much English do you have, my friend?
也许我们应该加深下了解
Maybe when we get to know each other better.
我要12个 我不要被干过的
I'll take a dozen, and I don't want them fucked out.
我定价格 维持费用你付
I set the rates. The upkeep's on him.
我认为维持费用是很低的
And my understanding is the upkeep is quite minimal.
很好 那就让他多拿点去打麻将吧
Good! Gives him more to spend on mahjong.
我就不问我们的安排中的偏袒了
I won't question the apparent one-sidedness of our arrangement.
不是你也不是李先生单独安排的
The arrangement is not yours and Mr Lee's alone.
是的 在我不了解的方法上
Yes, and in ways I don't understand...
让李先生在营地 肯定是让你
it must benefit you and the man whose name I must never say...
以及那位不能提名字的人获益了
to have Mr Lee in camp...
也许吴先生要出局了
and perhaps Mr Wu out of it...
可能会去见他的祖宗们
maybe among the spirits of his ancestors.
但是不管怎样祝福我 我都知道 最后都会到
But what a blessing for me, finally to reach a point in life...
那个我感觉不到的 生命的终点
where I don't feel I have to know.
一个后肢行走的动物
A creature walking around on hind legs.
就好像Crop Ear和六个伐木工那样
Just like Crop Ear and them half-dozen bushwhackers...
在森林里游荡
out in the forests...
一伙我喜欢或不喜欢的人 充斥着我每天的生活
ones I'd fall in with or out, whatever suited my daily purpose.
直到后来我遇到了AI
That's what I was till I crossed paths with Al.
Well 敲鼓弹琴吧 我会撕点衣服装点你
Well, bang the drum and play the pipes and I'll rend our fucking garments.
我就是说说
I was just saying.
今天下午我不想听忏悔
I ain't hearing confessions this afternoon.
答应我 你会和我一起烧了这里 Dan
Say you'll burn it down with me, Dan.
什么？
What?
这个该死的地方
This fucking place...
在Tolliver占有它之前
before letting Tolliver take it over.
行
Done.
Well,Jewel,张嘴说点
Well, open your mouth, Jewel, and say something...
我们听不懂的事吧
we can't fucking understand!
他在叫你
He's asking for you.
别和你的秘密一起死掉
Don't die with your fucking secret.
清理三号房 Dolly说她流血了
Clean the number three. Dolly said she bled.
该死的
God damn it!
我要来点威士忌 医生你要么？
I may get me a whiskey, Doc. You need any whiskey?
不 我不要威士忌
No, I do not want a fucking whiskey.
Well,也许能稳定你的手
Well, maybe as far as steadying the hand.
你怎么敢这样和我说话！ 闭嘴
How dare you? You shut your fucking mouth!
我没讽刺什么
I didn't mean nothing by it.
威士忌不会稳定我的手
Whiskey does not steady the hand.
它只是降低了对我的手是否颤抖的担心而已
It just dulls the worry over the hand's unsteadiness.
上帝啊 上帝啊 我不想杀了他
Jesus Christ! Jesus Christ, I do not need to kill another man!
擦
Fuck!
我的医药包的左上角
Top left corner of my fucking bag.
找什么？
For what?
香油 你的白痴 减轻你烫伤的持续疼痛
Balm, you fucking idiot, against the burn you fucking just sustained.
谢谢 医生
Thanks, Doc.
好的
All right.
-Dan -走开 吴
-Dan. -Go away, Wu.
-Swearengen. -没门
-Swearengen. -No.
-Swearengen. -Well  不会让你上去的
-Swearengen. -Well, it ain't gonna happen.
-Swearengen. -不  吴  他生病了
-Swearengen. -No, Wu! He's fucked up.
现在 AI不能和你讲话 我也不明白你在说啥
Now, Al can't talk to you right now, and I can't understand you...
所以你回Chink Alley吧
so you go the fuck back to Chink Alley!
别凭空瞎画 对我胡言乱语
Do not start drawing air to talk gibberish to me!
混蛋
Cocksucker!
-看在上帝的份上 -混蛋
-For Christ's sake. -Cocksucker!
你在浪费我的时间  吴
It's wasted on me, Wu.
混蛋  混蛋
Cocksucker! Cocksucker!
我不明白你的意思  吴  我没AI那么聪明
I don't get it, Wu. I am not as smart as Al.
现在有太多事等着我们去做呢
And there's too much on our fucking plate right now to deal with it.
-混蛋 旧金山  -上帝啊
-Cocksucker! San Francisco. -Jesus fucking Christ!
好吧 有个看不到的混蛋在你旁边
All right, there's an invisible cocksucker next to you...
他来自旧金山
and he's from San Francisco.
混蛋
Cocksucker.
-旧金山的混蛋 -我要
-San Francisco cocksucker. -I'm going with....
你想让我告诉AI有个混蛋…
You want me to tell Al that there's a cocksucker.
他看起来像
He looks like....
他长得像你 来自旧金山…
He looks like you and he's from San Francisco...
而且他惹火你了  我要上去了  我会告诉他的
and he's got your dander up. I'm going up now. I'll go tell him.
-告诉他什么？ -只有上帝晓得
-Tell him what? -God only knows.
为什么你不学美国话？
Why don't you learn to talk American?
能省掉我们很多麻烦
Save us all a lot of fucking trouble!
吴懂得英语
Wu know Englishing.
Adams先生 日安
Mr Adams? Good day.
日安  lsringhausen小姐
Good day, Miss lsringhausen.
我想不到你现在在想什么
I can't imagine what you must be thinking at the moment.
请进
Please, come in.
我能提供威士忌以及我刚洗过脸的水
I can offer you a whiskey or water that I just washed my face in.
我要威士忌 先生
I will have whiskey, sir.
好的
Sure.
我刚被解雇了 解雇了
I've just been discharged. Sacked!
被Garret夫人？
By Mrs Garret?
作为她的家庭教师
As tutor for her ward.
Well  我希望你打了她一拳
Well, I hope you punched her in the nose.
这是我第一次被雇主解雇后
This is a day of firsts. Dismissal from employment...
无人陪伴的待在男人的房间里
unchaperoned presence in a man's room.
对你的消息我感到遗憾  lsringhausen小姐
I'm sorry for your news, Miss lsringhausen...
但是如果这是你第一次喝酒的话
but if that's your first taste of liquor...
我很抱歉打乱了你一直以来的好习惯
I'm sorry for the hand you've been playing your whole life.
-你介意我直接用瓶子喝么？ -不介意 先生
-You mind if I drink from the bottle? -No, sir.
Oh 伙计
Oh, boy.
-Oh  伙计 -我很抱歉
-Oh, boy. -I'm sorry.
-你想让我出去么？ -这是你的房间
-You want me to get out of here? -It's your room.
没事 你又不是贼 或者你想让我打自己一枪
That's okay. You're not a thief. Or would you feel better if I shot myself?
你为什要这样说？
Why do you say that?
我道歉 这种开玩笑的方法很愚蠢
I apologise. It was just a stupid way of trying to be funny.
因为我害怕我被杀了
Because I fear I may be killed.
什么？
What?
我不能解释清楚
I can't explain.
噩梦 不可思议的
It's nightmarish. It's incomprehensible.
谁威胁你的生命了？
Who's threatening your life?
Garret夫人
Mrs Garret.
我知道这听起来不太可能
I know it sounds impossible...
但我能证明给你 Adams先生
but I can testify to you, Mr Adams...
我不是第一个被她杀死的人
I would not be the first person she's killed.
你想让我绑在上面还是下面？
You want I should tie him high or tie him low?
绑在上面
Tie him high.
我们要不要上去给他一剂麻醉  医生？
Should we go ahead and put a good fucking hit of dope down him, Doc?
好的 上去准备给他一支
Yeah, go ahead and get a hit ready.
AI  我要救你才做的手术
Al, I have to secure you for surgery!
怎么了 AI？
What is it, Al?
他害怕了
He's afraid.
你害怕了  AI？
You afraid, Al?
你害怕那把刀？
You've got a fear of the knife.
他想自然排石
He wants to try passing them stones natural.
你害怕么  AI？
Are you afraid, Al?
Oh  上帝啊 我压在他的坚硬的膀胱上了
Oh, God! I'm on his fucking nuts!
该死的  鼻盐是我们现在要用到的
God damn! Smelling salts is what we're going to administer!
你听见我说话了么 AI？
Do you hear me, Al?
这是一剂
Here is a fucking dose...
给你的鼻子的鼻盐
of smelling salts to your nose!
你在干嘛  医生？
What are you doing, Doc?
安静  扶他起来 把住他的脚
Be quiet! Sit him up and get him to his goddamn feet!
露出阴茎
Take his prick out!
来吧 来吧 AI
Come on! Come on, Al!
出来了 AI  出来了 AI
There you come, Al! There you come!
-就这样  你做到了 -就这样  AI
-There you go! You're doing it! -There you come, Al.
就这样  你个牛头混蛋
There you go, you ox-minded son of a gun!
-使劲 你个混蛋  使劲啊 -来啊 AI
-Push at it, you bastard! Push at it! -Come on, Al!
你尿的和马一样有力
You'd do a horse proud with the strength of that fucking stream!
放下他 把他放在床上
Lay him down. Lay Al down on the bed!
我们来照顾这个
We are gonna take care of this.
我要把这个插回去  帮你清理结石
I'm gonna put this instrument back inside you and clear that cocksucker...
你有进步了  我们不会切开你的
you've been making progress with, and we are not gonna cut you!
把膝盖弄到胸口  按住他
Bring his knee up to his chest. You hold him down.
-Johnny, 你去阳台吧 -我来拿着鼻盐
-Johnny, you go on out to the balcony. -I have charge of the salts!
好的
All right!
好的  我能感到我碰到石头了
All right! I can feel the fucking click of the gleet!
好的 现在 我要你挤他的阴茎
All right, now, I want you to milk his prick.
从上到下  我想让你把结石挤出来
From top to bottom, and I want you to bring that cocksucker down.
就是这样
That's it.
-哪里 来吧 AI
-There. -Come on, Al.
好的  看到了 一个接着一个的
All right! Look at it! One gleet chasing a-fucking-nother!
上帝保佑你  AI
God bless you, Al!
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你救了我 上帝
Thank you for saving me, God.
-你们不舒服了么 姑娘们？
-Are you uncomfortable, girls? -They're fine.
你付钱让她们站在那儿 W先生
You're paying them to stand in their position, Mr W...
她们会站在她们的位置上
they'll stand in their position.
之前她们摆过更难受的姿势
They've been in more awkward positions before.
在几千年前的塞浦路斯 女人们第一次
Thousands of years ago, in Cyprus, women went about their own lives...
在神庙卖淫后
only after first spending time as prostitutes...
才算是开始了自己的生活
at the temple of Aphrodite.
以滥交为贡品
The tribute of their promiscuity...
祈求女神保护岛屿 赐福作物
meant to secure for the island the goddess's grant of bountiful crops...
以及好的天气
and beautiful weather.
在比赛的祭坛上女人的生殖器是必备的祭品
Woman's generative instrument on the altar of the race's necessities...
从那以后我们就没再见过了
have we not come some far piece since then?
比如 你们谁还在祭坛上做爱？
Who, for example, fucks on altars anymore?
亦或假装这样能影响天气
Or pretends anything can make up the weather's mind?
Francis 今晚上你会干我么？
Are you gonna fuck me tonight, Francis?
我让Carrie感到厌烦了
I bore Carrie.
你在偷看 我让你别看了
You were peeking. I asked you not to look.
对不起
Sorry.
W先生  为什么你不去做你要做的事呢？
Why not just go do what you're gonna do, Mr W?
我现在不是在按计划做么？
Am I on a schedule then?
她是说我们的教学可以延后
She only meant our educations can wait.
换个夜晚我会很享受我们的谈话
I quite enjoyed our talk the other night.
-你想干她么？ -不 Carrie 不
-Do you want to fuck her? -No, Carrie. No.
否则我会说的
Or I'd say so.
房间里的气氛开始不利于我了
The atmosphere of the room turns against me.
不耐烦正凝聚在这个本应放纵享受的地方
A growing collective impatience where should be a haven of indulgence.
-你们不会满足我么？ -我们正在努力 W先生
-Won't you indulge me? -We're trying, Mr W.
但是你的行为恶劣
But you are behaving badly.
太令我失望了 本来我以为
Disappointing, from you
你很享受我的神话故事
who I thought to regale with details of the myths.
上帝
Gods fornicat私通凡人ing with mortals...
无尽的乱伦
the endless incest.
父亲淫乱女儿 淫乱姊妹
Fathers upon daughters upon sisters....
宠幸她或者离开这里
Take her in or get out, please.
-原谅我们吧 -当然
-Excuse us. -Of course.
请多包涵  我认为我让她不高兴了
Be generous. I think I've upset her.
-Well  你瞄准哪呢？ -你的乳头
-Well, whatever were you aiming at? -Your titties!
在你快洗完的时候这里出现了个机会  特派员
Any chance in here of an imminent finish, Commissioner?
我想你可能想传达给报纸编辑
My thought being you might want to deliver our newspaper editor...
一份文件证明 在他喝醉不能印出来之前
a certain document before he's too drunk to make it out.
我不想 除非我洗完澡
I think not, until my bath is finished.
我认为洗完包括
And I think a finish would involve...
你吹了气泡之下的某个东西 honey.
you blowing some of them bubbles underwater, honey.
Eamon.
他有机会从Gayville回来么 Dan
Has he per any fucking chance returned from Gayville, Dan...
或者说他从没去过？
which he had never been to?
AI在楼山
Al's upstairs.
现在如果你答应一些规矩 我就带你上去见他
Now if you agree to a few fucking rules, I'll give you a brief audience with him.
扮演老板感觉不好么 Dan？
Don't it feel good to play at boss, Dan?
除非你想坐在这儿 挑战的我胆量
Unless you want to sit down here and bust my fucking balls...
先不说你从没学过在文明人的社会里怎么生活
over you never learning to move amongst civilised people?
-现在 见AI更重要 -好的
-No, an audience is more important. -All right.
现在  在我们上去的时候你给我听仔细了
Now, you listen careful while we walk up.
你到了那 说你要抢劫
You get up there, you propose a robbery.
你告诉他地点
You give him the location...
你准备保证的收益
the take that you are prepared to guarantee...
AI的收益分成 以及超过预计的额外津贴
Al's fee on that take and then a bonus for overage.
然后你就闭嘴  Eamon,
And then, Eamon, you shut the fuck up.
AI过了很糟糕的一天
Al has had a tough fucking day.
Now  你让他指示给你他怎样选
Now, you let him indicate to you however he fucking chooses...
就是 是 或者 不是
as to "yes" or a "no."
现在就公平了 不是么？
Now that's fair, ain't it?
你是个伟人 Dan 你是伟人啊
You're a great man, Dan. It's you that's the great one.
别挑战我的胆量
Don't bust my fucking balls.
别叫我Crop Ear, 你个没胆的傻逼
Don't call me "Crop Ear," you gutless son of a bitch.
Eamon,  我们过着自己选择的生活
Eamon, we live life however we choose.
你却活的像个站在吧台后的婊子
And you choose life as a cunt standing behind a bar.
-只是想帮你个忙 -我没用你帮忙
-Just trying to do you a fucking favour. -I'll have no favours from you!
好吧 那么 Crop Ears.
All right, then. Crop Ears.
或者你想被叫做别的什么
Or whatever the fuck it is you want to be called!
想试探AI的恢复情况 那就帮你个忙吧
Trying to gauge Al's recovery and do you a fucking favour.
Crop Ears要死在那了么？
Crop Ears is dying up there.
把他带到中国佬那里去 你扔了他
Take him over to the Chinaman's and you throw him away.
好的 Dan 好的
Sure, Dan. Sure.
Yeah  我去拿滑犁
Yeah, I'll go get the sled.
我没耐心干这破事
I don't have the patience for this fucking bullshit!
我也过了糟糕的一天
I have had a tough fucking day!
你去看亲戚了  Carrie？
Were you seeing a relative, Carrie?
还是老鸨想扣留你 阻止我
Or did the madam withhold you to frustrate me?
她没告诉我为什么这样做
She doesn't tell me why she does things.
但你知道你是不是去看亲戚了
But you'd know if you were seeing a relative.
是的  我没有
Yes. I wasn't.
那你去看谁了？
Were you seeing anyone?
一个印第安人 我和他做爱 也和他的马做
A wild lndian. I fucked him and I fucked his horse.
你讨厌这里
You hate it here.
我猜你不
I suppose you don't.
是的 我不讨厌这里
I don't, no.
[他是地质学家]
岩石给我讲故事
The rocks tell me stories.
现在我有了你
And now I have you.
Well 我没疯 所以它们没给我讲故事
Well, I'm not a crazy person, so they don't talk to me.
我就是我  所以我希望在纽约
And I'm with me wherever I am, so I wish I was in fucking New York.
岩石没有告诉我 是我学习着它们的故事
The rocks don't "talk" to me, but still I learn their stories.
Oh  我明白了  多谢你告诉我这些
Oh, I understand now. Thank you for saying it
好像我是个孩子似的
like I'm a baby.
Well
Well....
-这些山有着无法想象的财富  -那又怎样呢？
-These hills are unimaginably rich. -So what?
吸引了像我老板那样的游荡猎食者的注意力
To compel even the vagrant attentions of someone like my employer.
我不会为了大量财富就留下来的
I won't stay for any amount.
为了大量财富 那你会为了少量的钱留下来么？
For a large amount, will you stay for a little?
现在就给我
Give me some now.
当然可以
Of course.
比我给老鸨的多
It's more than I gave the madam.
你不能像对待其他人那样打我
And you mustn't hit me like you do the others.
你没让我不愉快
You have never displeased me.
别打我 Francis.
Don't fucking hit me, Francis.
好的  我同意
Done. Agreed.
我跑到了印第安人那里
I will run away to the lndians.
你会改变历史进程的
You would change the course of history.
成为第一个女首领
Be the first of the women chiefs.
我射的太快了
I'm too quick.
对我来说不快
You can't be too quick for me.
什么时候你可以试试把阴茎掏出来
You might try it sometime with your prick outside of your pants.
我感觉Stubbs小姐有个亲戚
I sense Miss Stubbs has fucked a relative.